<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Learning on Naim Shant Trial</title>
    <link>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep Learning on Naim Shant Trial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:03:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Data Science Salary Estimator</title>
      <link>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/proect-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:03:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/proect-1/</guid>
      <description>Created a tool that estimates data science salaries (MAE ~ $ 11K) to help data scientists negotiate their income when they get a job. Scraped over 1000 job descriptions from glassdoor using python and selenium Engineered features from the text of each job description to quantify the value companies put on python, excel, aws, and spark. Optimized Linear, Lasso, and Random Forest Regressors using GridsearchCV to reach the best model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Ball Image Classifier</title>
      <link>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:02:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this example project I built a ball classifier to identify balls from different sports. This could be useful for someone who is new to sports from a certain country. They could take a picture of a ball and an app could serve them some information about the history and rules of the game. This is the underlying model for building something with those capabilities.
I was able to get the model to predict the sport of the ball with 94% accuracy after minimal tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3</title>
      <link>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:01:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/project/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris,   on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iamshant.github.io/shant_portfolio_2/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me in the social media platforms
   Platforms URL     youtube: https://youtube.com   github: https://github.com/iamshant    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
